这是一个真实的故事
THIS IS A TRUE STORY
艺术家路易斯·韦恩
The artist Louis Wain
这只猫是他自己的。
made the cat his own.
他发明了猫的风格，
He invented a cat style,
猫会，
a cat society,
整个猫的世界。
a whole cat world.
看起来和生活都不像路易·韦恩猫的猫
Cats that do not look and live like Louis Wain cats
他们为自己感到羞耻。
are ashamed of themselves.
但这并不重要。
But that is not what is important.
重要的是路易斯·韦恩献出了他的一生
What is important is that Louis Wain devoted his life
让我们的生活更幸福，
to making all our lives happier,
而且更牛。
and cattier.
他这样做无疑是在社会上养大了猫
In doing so, he undoubtedly raised up the cat in society
他让我们的世界变得更好。
and he changed our world for the better.
除了奇怪的社会偏见
Aside from its bizarre social prejudices
事实上一切都是狗屎味，
and the fact that everything stank of shit,
维多利亚时代的英国也是一个创新之地
Victorian England was also a land of innovation
和科学发现。
and scientific discovery.
世界上许多最优秀的人
Many of the world’s finest minds